{
  "reference_number": "8396",
  "clauses": [
    {
      "question": "1. What process should the Government use to set a new emissions reduction target in legislation?",
      "question_index": 0,
      "answer": null,
      "answer_index": 5,
      "notes": "The Government should get out of the Paris Accord .It is founded on ''Failed old science'''"
    },
    {
      "question": "2. If the Government sets a 2050 target now, which is the best target for New Zealand?",
      "question_index": 1,
      "answer": null,
      "answer_index": 5,
      "notes": "All three options are based on the failed science that CO2 and other trace greenhouse gases are the ''control knob of our\n\n climate''That is false.The sun governs climate ,warming and cooling [Svensmark et al.]"
    },
    {
      "question": "3. How should New Zealand meet its targets?",
      "question_index": 2,
      "answer": null,
      "answer_index": 5,
      "notes": "''There is no data from thousands and millions of years to show that extra CO2 causes warming or for that matter cooling'' A quote\n\n from Astrophysicist Prof Piers Corbyn.It is factually correct."
    },
    {
      "question": "4. Should the Zero Carbon Bill allow the 2050 target to be revised if circumstances change?",
      "question_index": 3,
      "answer": "Yes",
      "answer_index": 3,
      "notes": "Yes .certainly.The climate has already started to cool as predicted by the Astrophysicists [0.6 degrees Centigrade since Feb 2016\n U.A.H. data] The little ice age has begun and by 2021 there will be no doubt that Extra CO2 does NOT cause warming .We can then\n get out of the Paris Accord"
    },
    {
      "question": "5. The Government proposes that three emissions budgets of five years each (i.e. covering the next 15 years) be in place at any given time. Do you agree with this proposal?",
      "question_index": 15,
      "answer": "No",
      "answer_index": 8,
      "notes": "We must be planning to get out of the Paris accord .It is based on failed old science.The sooner we get out the better.Already\n ''laboratory planet earth'' is proving Dangerous anthropogenic global warming a LIE"
    },
    {
      "question": "6. Should the Government be able to alter the last emissions budget (i.e. furthest into the future)?",
      "question_index": 4,
      "answer": "Yes - each incoming Government should have the option to review the third budget in the sequence",
      "answer_index": 14,
      "notes": "The failed science of D.A.G.W. is already being exposed by Nature,experiment, experience.Every government must be allowed out of\n\n The Paris accord .So that we can follow America's lead.They know the sun not CO2 governs climate"
    },
    {
      "question": "7. Should the Government have the ability to review and adjust the second emissions budget within a specific range under exceptional circumstances? See p36 Our Climate Your Say",
      "question_index": 5,
      "answer": "Yes",
      "answer_index": 3,
      "notes": "Yes When there is NO doubt that we are cooling fast [if we had an honest media that would already be crystal clear] then we will all\n want out."
    },
    {
      "question": "13. The Government has proposed that Climate Change Commissioners need to have a range of essential and desirable expertise. Do you agree with the proposed expertise? See p45 Our Climate Your Say",
      "question_index": 11,
      "answer": "Yes",
      "answer_index": 3,
      "notes": "The government and it's advisers ''Climate Change Commissioners'' are all getting their advice from failed group think scientists like\nthose at Victoria, I.P.C.C. and N.I.W.A..They Still believe CO2 governs climate .That is Wrong.Solar ''charged particle flux'' is the controler\n\nof climate"
    },
    {
      "question": "14. Do you think the Zero Carbon Bill should cover adapting to climate change?",
      "question_index": 12,
      "answer": "No",
      "answer_index": 8,
      "notes": "We know what to expect from climate change.As Galactic cosmic ray influx increases heavy precipitation events will become more\nintense and common .Our jet streams are no longer guided by our magnetosphere.it has weakened so much already as sun spot\n\nactivity falls away"
    },
    {
      "question": "15. The Government has proposed a number of new functions to help us adapt to climate change. Do you agree with the proposed functions? See p47 Our Climate Your Say",
      "question_index": 13,
      "answer": "No",
      "answer_index": 8,
      "notes": "Climate change is not of our making we have no control over it.We must stop our government believing that we cause climate change\nby burning fosill fuel.We must get through to them ''THE SUN GOVERNS CLIMATE''"
    },
    {
      "question": "16. Should we explore setting up a targeted adaptation reporting power that could see some organisations share information on their exposure to climate change risks?",
      "question_index": 14,
      "answer": "Yes",
      "answer_index": 3,
      "notes": "Only if they realise that we know what climate change will bring .The Grand Solar Minimum,climate change that is and we relay do not\n\nknow for New Zealand.But there is plenty of data from The Northern Hemisphere 1600 onwards The ''little ice age'' We know sea level\nrise is slowing and will almost certainly start to fall .extreme precipitation events yes .maritime.So cold won't be a problem"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you have any other comments you'd like to make?",
      "question_index": 16,
      "answer": null,
      "answer_index": 5,
      "notes": "Yes if you want to know more about the Astrophysicist's science that DOES explain Climate Change.Contact me William Partridge\nB.Sc. can do lecture or debate Yours Sincerely Will"
    }
  ]
}
